ASIF SYED

Master's in Business Analytics & Data Science student at Oklahoma State University

https://linktr.ee/asifsyd | +1-405-894-2106 | asif.syed@okstate.edu

CAREER SUMMARY:

I am a current Master's student at Oklahoma State University, actively looking for summer internship opportunities to gain relevant industry experience in the data science & analytics fields. I have four years of work experience in SAP consulting, during which I developed an ability to scale up quickly in new roles and environments.

WORK EXPERIENCE:

Deloitte Consulting, India

SAP Customer Service Consultant | Nov, 2021 - Jul, 2022

Proactively identified and fixed issues with a healthcare sector client's automatic invoicing
in its SAP ERP system. It ensured close to 95% success rate of invoice transmissions to this
client's customers in the later months..

Infosys Limited, India

SAP Supply Chain Management Consultant | Jul, 2021 - Nov, 2022

 Assisted a global client in the consumer electronics sector by implementing a new order fulfillment method in its SAP ERP. Approximately 15% of new orders generated in its client system today

Accenture, India

SAP Master Data Analyst | May, 2018 - Jul, 2021

 Successfully automated the process of master data creation in SAP with the help of a VBA Macro in Excel that automates the task of copy-pasting data from Excel to SAP for an American client that deals with the household cleaning supplies business

RELEVANT PROJECTS:

Data Cleaning from JSON files for creating an exhaustive T20I cricket dataset.

GitHub Link: https://github.com/Asif1310/3009

Skills used: Python, Working with JSON data and Data Cleaning.

EDUCATION:

2022 - 2024 | Oklahoma State University, United States

Master's in Business Analytics & Data Science

2014-2018 | Chaitanya Bharathi Inst. of Tech, India

Bachelor's of Engineering in Civil Engineering

SKILLS:

Python, MySQL, Tableau, and Microsoft Excel.